(Howard:)Sheldon, don't take this the wrong way,
but you're insane.
(Leonard:)That may well be, but the fact is it
wouldn't kill us to meet some new people.
(Sheldon:)For the record,
it could kill us to meet new people.
(Sheldon:)They could be murderers
or the carriers of unusual pathogens.
(Sheldon:)And I'm not insane.
My mother had me tested.
(Leonard:)If we do get a new friend,
he should be a guy you can trust.
You know, a guy who has your back.
He should have money and live in a cool
place by the beach where we throw parties.
- He should share our love of technology.
- And he should know a lot of women.
Okay, let's see, money, women, technology.
Okay, we're agreed.
(Leonard:)Our new friend is going to be Iron Man.
RAJESH [SINGING]:
I can go all night
If you know what I mean
(Raj:)Welcome to the Raj Mahal.
Yes, it's very nice. Good night, Raj.
(Raj:)- Wait, the evening's not over.
- Yes, it is.